{
    "q1": {
                "question": " Which built-in method combines the text of two strings and returns a new string?",
                "options": [
                    "append()",
                    "concat()",
                    "attach()",
                    "None of the above."
                ],
                "answer": "concat()"
            },
    "q2": {
                "question": "Which built-in method returns the string representation of the number's value?",
                "options": [
                    "toValue()",
                    "toNumber()",
                    "toString()",
                    "None of the above."
                ],
                "answer": "toString()"
            },
    "q3": {
                "question": " Which of the following tag represents the header of a section in HTML5?",
                "options": [
                    "section",
                    "article",
                    "aside",
                    "header"
                ],
                "answer": "header"
            },
    "q4": {
                "question": "Which of the following jQuery method removes an attribute from each of the matched elements?",
                "options": [
                    "deleteAttr( name )",
                    " removeAttr( name )",
                    "removeAttribute( name )",
                    "None of the above."
                ],
                "answer": "removeAttr( name )"
            },
    "q5": {
                "question": " Which of the following type of variable takes precedence over other if names are same?",
                "options": [
                    "global variable",
                    "local variable",
                    "Both of the above",
                    "None of the above."
                ],
                "answer": "local variable"
            },
    "q6": {
                "question": "Which built-in method returns the calling string value converted to upper case?",
                "options": [
                    "toUpperCase()",
                    "toUpper()",
                    "changeCase(case)",
                    "None of the above."
                ],
                "answer": "toUpperCase()"
            },
    "q7": {
                "question": "Which of the following attribute is used to group elements?",
                "options": [
                    "item",
                    "itemprop",
                    "itemcheck",
                    "itemgroup"
                ],
                "answer": "item"
            },
    "q8": {
                "question": "Which of the following function of Array object represents the source code of an object?",
                "options": [
                    "toSource()",
                    "splice()",
                    "oString()",
                    "unshift()"
                ],
                "answer": "toSource()"
            },
    "q9": {
                "question": "Which of the following input control is used for input fields that should contain an URL address in Web Form 2.0?",
                "options": [
                    "email",
                    "URL",
                    "number",
                    "range"
                ],
                "answer": "URL"
            },
    "q10": {
                "question": "Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be italic, as if it were in an <i> tag?",
                "options": [
                    "fixed()",
                    "fontcolor()",
                    "fontsize()",
                    "italics()"
                ],
                "answer": "italics()"
            }
}